There's one trading rule that completely
transformed the way that I approached
the market. It is simple, it works every
single week, and it's allowed me to have
consistent profits while most traders
[music] stay stuck taking loss after
loss. What most people don't see is that
I was prepared. I wasn't just rushing.
[music] I waited, I traded the exact
setup, I didn't overtrade, and I took
the win and ran with it. Most traders
take 10, 15, [music] even 20 trades a
week, but me? No. I made over $10,000
last week only taking one [music] trade
every single morning, only trading the
first hour every single morning. So, I
work less and I make more than most
[music] traders. So, in this video, I
want to teach you the exact one trade
per day strategy that I use every single
[music] morning. It is simple,
mechanical, repeatable, no fancy
indicators, no bloat, no thousand
different criteria. No. You'll be able
to start using this strategy every
single morning. Let's get into it. Quick
disclaimer, trading is not a
get-rich-quick scheme. It took me years
of losing before I finally learned and
became consistent. Always trade at your
own risk. Never risk money you cannot
afford to lose. I am not a financial
advisor. This is strictly for
educational purposes only. Most traders
think that the more trades you take, the
more money you'll make, but that is a
complete myth. Overtrading is one of the
biggest killers that somebody can have
to their account. [music] Because let me
break it down for you. We take one
trade. If you win, and then you take
another trade, and then you lose some of
the profits, you are going to get mad.
And then what's going to happen is
you're probably going to take another
trade, another trade, another trade,
again this bad spiral of losing, losing,
losing, losing, then doing stupid
[music] things, oversizing, and it never
ends well. Now, same thing, if you take
a loss, and then you take another trade
for no reason, and take another loss,
then you're sitting with a big red for
the day. You can't sit with it. You get
mad. You then take another trade, you
oversize, and before you know it, your
account [music] is cut in half just
because you weren't okay accepting a
small red day. Now, that is why
overtrading is one of the biggest
[music] account killers that I've seen.
So, one thing that you need to keep in
mind with this strategy is that it's all
about day-by-day staying [music]
disciplined, focusing on the only the
high-quality setups, and it's okay if
you lose some days because I've
personally had about a 70% win rate with
this strategy. I'm telling you guys, one
trade a day can genuinely change the
trajectory of your whole trading
journey. Because when you're taking one
trade a day, you're waiting. You're
being patient. You're only taking the
[music] setup that looks A+. And that
means a lot. It's going to help you
avoid dumb trades, FOMO trades, and
doing stuff that you know should not be
done. And [music] look, you might be
thinking to yourself like you'll see
you'll go in the market, you see a move,
or you think something's going to
happen, but there's no setup, and then
it might happen, you might get mad, but
the next time it happens, you're going
to take the trade, and you're going to
lose.
Guys, the day you understand that you
don't need to catch every single move is
the [music] day where you get one step
closer to becoming profitable. I don't
care if the market has the craziest
moves up, down, blah blah blah, I don't
care. All I care about is following my
system and catching that same chunk
every single day. I don't want to catch
the bottom, I don't want to catch the
top the top, but I just want to catch
the the crumbs, the consistent [music]
chunk that I could get every day. Now,
let's get into my strategy. So, as you
guys can see on my chart, there's this
red area, then there's this black area.
Now, what are my settings here? This is
called the pre- and post-market hours.
The red area is the pre-market. The
pre-market is very, very important for
me. Every morning, what I like to do is
I like to mark the top of the
pre-market, and then I like to mark the
bottom of the pre-market. [music]
Now, this is my range for the day.
>> [music]
>> So,
if it's above the pre-market high,
that's when I could focus on a long
trade or calls. And if it's under
pre-market low, that's when I can focus
on a short trade or puts. But if it's
[music] in between, then I do not focus
on it.
Today is a perfect example of a day
where I wouldn't take any trades [music]
because you mark the pre-market high,
you mark the pre-market low. And what
happened? We stayed in between the
pre-market high and the pre-market low
all day. If we're in between the
pre-market high and the pre-market low,
that means to me that it's [music] a
chop day. I don't like to trade chop
days. These are annoying, bad days, not
consistent moves, and just
bad days to trade, not A+ trading
conditions. These pre-market high and
these pre-market low, this is like your
boundaries, okay?
This is like your boundaries.
>> [music]
>> So,
we need to understand that if the price
is not above market high, then these
this level
this stock this price action means
nothing to you for the upside because
you can't trade it above unless it's
above pre-market high
>> [music]
>> for calls. And if it's not under
pre-market low, you cannot trade it for
downside, either. [music] So, you always
mark your pre-market high and your
pre-market low, and these are your
levels for the day. Now, let me go over
what [music] I'm looking for for an
actual trade.
So, every morning when I mark that
pre-market high and I mark the
pre-market low, I'm looking for the
stock to close [music] either above the
pre-market high
or for the stock to close [music]
Let's mark our pre-market high and
pre-market low here.
Or or the stock to close
under the pre-market low.
So, as you can see here, [music] the
stock closes above the pre-market high
here on the 5-minute time frame. And as
you can see here, the stock closes under
the pre-market low on the 5-minute time
frame. [music]
Now,
what am I looking for?
After the stock closes the 5-minute
above, that is your confirmation.
>> [music]
>> So, here's in my confirmation for calls
or longs, and here's in my confirmation
for puts or [music] shorts. But, what I
look for after this is interesting. So,
now I'm looking for the retest. The
retest is when the stock comes back and
taps that level.
But, I'm not entering exactly when it
taps. [music]
I'm entering once it taps and then
starts to go up a little bit. I want to
see a little bit of momentum to come in.
So, we can go on the 1-minute. I can
show you how we do the exact time where
I would enter this trade.
So,
here,
I'm not entering right
>> [music]
>> here on this tap. I'm not entering right
there, but I'm probably entering like
right here once it goes up a little bit
for the calls.
Now, for the downside, same thing.
We can go back to the 1-minute here.
I don't trade in the 1-minute, guys.
This is to show you like candle by
candle
when I would enter the trade.
So, look.
I'm not pa- I'm not entering right here,
but I'm probably entering like right
here once it goes down a little bit.
So, that basically confirms to me that
momentum has came back into the trade
and that it's [music] to my favor. And
this basically helped me avoid something
where like the stock just [music] goes
boom straight above the level.
So,
you wait for the pre-market high retest.
And on this pre-market high retest, this
is
the entry. Oh, shoot. Wrong time frame.
So,
on the pre-market high retest, we enter.
>> [music]
>> And then there is a couple things that
you can do.
I personally like to put my stop loss if
it closes [music] under it.
And then
I like to [music] trim at new high day
then as it goes up. And then there's a
couple of different things you could
use. For the sake of this video, we're
going to use this 8 EMA. As long as the
stock doesn't get under the 8 EMA,
you could [music] stay in the trade. So,
this right here, if you were wrong, you
probably would have been like right I
don't know, maybe like right there or
something.
It's about a 1:7 risk to reward. Well,
actually, let's pull it to the EMA.
It's about a 1:5 risk to reward. You
would have entered on this retest.
You would have exited here, but you
would have taken trims in the layup. So,
like right here, I'm taking trims and
I'm moving my stop loss to in the
profits so that I do not lose in the
trade.
>> [music]
>> And as it goes up, I'm taking more off
and more off and more off. Now, same
thing here.
Probably entering the trade. And now
this one did close above a little bit,
but the next candle was a straight down.
So, when it like barely closes above
like this, what I like to do is say no
higher. So, basically like it closed
right here, like
10 cents above. Uh it's since it's so so
little, I'll be like, all right, if it
gets any higher, I'll get out. It didn't
get any higher. And then as you could
see, [music] so the stop would have been
right there, any higher. As you could
see, you would have absolutely crushed
this trade for a 1:14 risk to reward on
this.
>> [music]
>> If you were to put in 500 bucks, you
would probably have made over $2,000 on
this trade.
Crazy.
So, this is what these retests look
[music] like. Now, something to keep in
on keep in mind here, this is also a
VWAP retest. [music]
Now, I usually only trade VWAP retests
when it's either like way under
pre-market low or above pre-market high,
but when it's lined up with this
pre-market low or pre-market high, that
is a really, really, really good setup.
So, let me show you guys what you need
to also do with my strategy is you need
to add the VWAP on your charts. So, what
I'm going to do is I'm going to add the
VWAP.
Now, I'm going to click the three dots,
[music] go to settings, I'm going to
turn off upper band, turn off lower
band, turn off bands fill. I'm going to
make this yellow. I'm going to click
okay. And then,
what I'm going to still do, I'm going to
mark the pre-market high. Now, the times
that we trade VWAP is if the stock gets
way above pre-market high
with no retest. So, you see here how we
get a 5-minute close
above pre-market high
>> [music]
>> and then VWAP is over pre-market high.
When you have VWAP above pre-market
high, that means we're only focusing on
a VWAP retest. So, this right here would
be the entry once it comes down and taps
VWAP then goes up a little bit.
Then, we would have sold most of our
position once it got to the new high of
day.
And then, let's [music] see where the
EMA is. Would have probably gotten out
the rest at about right here. Still an
amazing trade, about 1:5 risk to reward.
So,
uh about 1:3 risk reward. That's for
your runners though, because keep in
mind guys, like after that new high day,
you're you're taking most off at this
new high day here or this high day test.
So, you're trading the VWAP retest when
the VWAP is above the pre-market high.
Now look, I want to give a special shout
out to Tradovate. Tradovate is one of
the best futures prop firms and I'm also
partnered with them. I've currently
gotten over $5,000 in payouts from
Tradovate and you can use code new age
and get 40% off. Tradovate has instant
funding, daily payouts, and no
activation fees. It's honestly amazing.
Also, after I think it's three or five
payouts, you can become a live trader or
they'll give you real life capital to
trade with. I really love what they're
doing and one of my favorite things
about Tradovate is the community aspect.
They host sick tournaments for their
traders. They're like live all the time
and the accounts, like I'm not just
promoting something that I don't like.
They sent you four payouts totaling
$5,150.
So, practicing what I preach. These are
all on a daily account and
unfortunately, I got a couple payouts on
it and then I blew it, but like imagine
you have a 150k select daily account,
right? All you have to do to pass it is
have like three winning days of 3,000
each on the account, then it's passed
and then you get daily payouts. So,
every day you win, you can withdraw,
withdraw, withdraw, withdraw. There's
like no rules that you have to do. You
just have to stay above the buffer and
it's freaking amazing. So, if you guys
want to try out Tradovate, use code new
age for 40% off. Send me proof after. I
have a bunch of accounts that I always
like to give away. And yeah, now here's
another example.
Stock gets above pre-market high, VWAP
is above pre-market high, you get a VWAP
retest.
You would have entered it here.
No reason to get out. Didn't have a new
high of the day.
Or you could have entered it here also.
Then all the way up. Huge huge huge
trade.
Over a 1 to 11 risk reward on this one.
Because it was stayed above. With that
So look, once it gets that high days
when you start to use the EMA. So here
it's kind of like chopping, whatever,
but then here is when you start to
understand like all right, this is when
I'm going to use the EMA.
>> [music]
>> Because
that you only do that after the first
trim.
Because before your first trim or your
even your second trim, like use the EMA
in the dominance of your runners, if
that makes sense.
So there's four setups, guys. There's
the pre-market high retest right here.
There's the pre-market low retest right
here. It's also a bearish view up retest
right here.
Now I'll show you guys something. Like
an example, another view up retest could
have been here, but if it's above the
EMA, I don't really like to take these.
But technically like if you were to take
this view up retest, you would have
lost, but that's okay. It would have
been a very small loss.
Here you would have lost.
Here let's see. You would have tried to
take view up puts here, target low of
day, you would have ended up losing.
Maybe 50 cents. And on this trade,
[music]
you would have made $7. So very very
great risk reward.
And then you have the bullish view up
retest. And there's also bearish view up
retest.
Which is just don't have an example
here, but uh
Yeah.
Here would be an example of like a loss
on that if you were to take it. Now
guys, keep in mind I just showed you
guys the strategy. I showed you guys
when to buy, when to sell, but it's also
very important that you guys stick to
it. I don't care about what happens
today, but what I care about is what
happens every day for the next two,
three, four, five years. I know that if
I stick [music] to it, then I'll be
good. So, I have to forget about the
short-term stuff. I just have to make
sure I'm my best performance, execute it
precisely,
>> [music]
>> and I stick to only this. You need to
treat your trading like a business, not
like a video game. And treating [music]
it like a business is going to basically
incur with a couple things. Keeping your
losses small, [music] following the
blueprint of what actually works, and
constantly adapting to what's not
working. So, if one day I see that, all
right, I journaled my trades for the
last couple months, and on this stock I
keep losing
>> [music]
>> because it's just the retest aren't
working, then what am I going to do? I'm
probably going to not trade on that
stock. You need to be constantly
adapting because the market's going to
be constantly adapting. And the way you
do that is through journaling. When I
started trading, my mindset was, I want
to make this much money every week. I
want to do this, do that. But now I
don't care about them. My mindset is
completely I just want to take good
trades with good risk reward, and put
myself in position to win in the long
term. So, stop focusing about the month,
stop focusing about the quarter, just
zoom out, and focus on [music] executing
the strategy that you know works, only
taking high risk reward trades, being
[music] disciplined every single day,
and becoming the best trader, and the
money will follow. So, stop chasing
these money goals, instead chase the I'm
going to become the best possible trader
I could goals, and that is how you're
going to become the best possible
[music] trader. Because now you put
yourself in a position where, instead of
chasing money,
you're chasing being the best trader,
and money's going to chase you. So,
guys, quality over quantity is key.
Patience over excitement is important,
and one boring trade a day can change
everything for you. So, guys, that's the
strategy. It's simple, repeatable, and I
mean, as you guys can see, it's nothing
too hard. Mark your pre-market levels,
you wait for it to get a 5-minute close
either over or under, then you trade the
retest. And if VWAP is over the
pre-market levels or under the
pre-market low, you trade the VWAP
retest. That is literally it. I hope you
guys enjoyed. I'm actually doing a free
training this Tuesday [music]
at 7:00 p.m. Eastern. The link is below
if you want to register. Basically,
we'll be going over the exact blueprint
on how you could become a better trader.
How I've done it and what I would do if
I was in your shoes. You could also ask
anything on the free live class. So, I'd
love to have you guys there. It's
completely free. It'll also be live, so.
Love you guys. I'll see you guys on the
class and subscribe. I post every single
Sunday at 3:00 p.m. Eastern. I really
hope you guys enjoy these videos that I
make. My goal is to motivate aspiring so
you guys that if I can do it, then you
could, too. [music] I'm blessed to have
this gift that be able to teach and I'm
going to keep spreading it.
Peace.